You can get a little bleeding after you take the tablet.
The next round of tablets you can take home or at the reception.
You and the healthcare staff agree on this at your first visit.
Insert the tablets into the vagina.
You need to lie still for at least 15 minutes after you have brought up the tablets.
You can feel bad and get a fever and chill, it is common and nothing is dangerous.
You start bleeding two to four hours after taking the tablets,
But sometimes it can take longer.
Take the last tablets after three hours.
You take the tablets whether you have started to bleed or not.
Insert the tablets into the vagina.
After the abortion it is common to bleed for one to two weeks
But how long and how much you bleed varies.
If you are early in pregnancy, you will bring a pregnancy test home.
The pregnancy test you do three to four weeks after the abortion.
You do the test to make sure you are not pregnant anymore.
It is important that you start with contraceptives immediately after the abortion, if you are going to have sex.